Guide to the Charles W. Duncan, Jr. business papers, 1958-2013 MS 583
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Charles W. Duncan, Jr. business papers
1958-2013
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Duncan, Charles William Jr.
MS 583
33 Linear Feet (32 boxes + 1 oversized box)
The Charles W. Duncan, Jr. business papers include correspondence, speeches and writings, memoranda, minutes, reports, studies, printed matter, photographs, memorabilia, newsclippings, and bound volumes. A 1947 graduate of Rice Institute, Duncan served under President Carter as Deptury Secretary of Defense and Secretary of Energy. He served as president of Coca-Cola, Co. and on the board of trustees of Rice University.
Biographical / Historical
Charles William Duncan, Jr. was born September 9, 1926, in Houston, Texas. He attended Rice Institute, where he majored in chemical engineering, served as an aviation cadet of the U. S. Army Air Force during 1944-46, and graduated with his B.S. degree in 1947. Following a stint as a roustabout and chemical engineer for Humble Oil and Refining Company (now Exxon); he joined his family's coffee importing and roasting firm, Duncan Foods Company, which produced Maryland Club Coffee. He married Anne Smith in 1957 and they have two children. Duncan Foods merged with Coca-Cola in 1964 and he worked as head of their European operations. He was elected president of the company in 1971. President Jimmy Carter, whom Mr. Duncan had gotten to know in Atlanta, brought him to the national capital to serve as Deputy Secretary of the U. S. Department of Defense from January 1977 to August 1979, at which point Mr. Duncan joined the president's cabinet as Secretary of the Department of Energy from August 1979 to January 1981, when President Carter left office.
After his government appointment ended, Duncan returned to Houston and established Gulf Partners (now Duncan Interests), an investment firm. Charles Duncan served many years as a Rice University trustee, including chairing the Rice Board of Trustees from 1982 to 1996, when he became chairman emeritus. Rice University's 11th residential college was named in honor of Charles and Anne Duncan as is Duncan Hall. He continues to participate in professional activities in Duncan Interests and philanthropic activities.
Scope and Contents
The Charles W. Duncan, Jr. business papers include correspondence, speeches and writings, memoranda, minutes, reports, studies, printed matter, photographs, memorabilia, newsclippings, and bound volumes. The papers are divided into four series covering the periods Duncan was head of Duncan Foods Company and president of Coca-Cola Co., 1958-1996; member and chair of Rice University's Board of Trustees, 1972-1996; and Deputy Secretary of U.S. Department of Defense and Secretary of the Department of Energy, 1977-1981. The fifth series includes drafts of his book, Three lives: a memoir published in 2013.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Conditions Governing Access
The bulk of this material is open for research; however, some files are restricted as noted.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection was donated by Charles W. Duncan, Jr in 2011-2014.
Index Terms
Subjects
Business; Politics and government; Rice University -- History; Universities and colleges
Document Types
typescripts; documents; memorabilia; scrapbooks; corrrespondence; photographs
- Series I. Business Interests: Duncan Foods, Coca-Cola, Co., and others, 1958-1996, 160578
  - Duncan Foods, 161648
    - Admiration and Maryland Club Coffees: Advertising and Promotion, vol. 1, 1958; 161627 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - Admiration and Maryland Club Coffees: Advertising and Promotion, vol. 2, 1958; 161628 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
    - New Concept in Marketing, vol. 1, 1959; 161641 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
    - New Concept in Marketing, vol. 2, 161642 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
    - New Concept in Marketing, vol. 3, 161644 (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
    - New Concept in Marketing, vol. 4, 161645 (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
    - New Concept in Marketing, vol. 5, 161646 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - New Concept in Marketing, vol. 6, 161649 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - This is your advertising agency handbook, 1961; 161652 (Box 1, Folder 15-16)
    - Observations and Recommendations, vol. 1, 1961-1962; 161654 (Box 1, Folder 17-18)
    - Observations and Recommendations, vol. 2, 1961-1962; 161657 (Box 1, Folder 19-20)
    - Observations and Recommendations, vol. 3, 1961-1962; 161659 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
    - Observations and Recommendations, vol. 4, 1961-1962; 161660 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Duncan Foods Co. Book no. 1, 161661 (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
    - Duncan Foods Supervisor's Personnel Policy Manual, 161662 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
  - Coca-Cola, Co., 161663
    - Annual Report, 1993; 161664 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Advertising: Commercial Buy the world a Coke, 161665 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Advertising policy, 1971-72; 161666 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Advertising: Miscellaneous, 1971-1973; 161667 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Atlanta, 1973; 161668 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Audit Committee, 1990; 161675 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Audit Committee Binder, 1994; 161669 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Audit Committee of the Board of Directors, 1998; 161670 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Audit Committee Meeting, October 19, 1989; 161671 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Audit Committee Meeting Minutes, [1988], 1994; 161672 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - [Ernst & Whinney] Audit Plan, 1988; 161673 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - [Preliminary] Audit Scope, 1990; 161674 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Corporate Auditing Department, 1989; 161676 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Boards: Coca-Cola Co. Meeting, November 16, 1970; 161677 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Boards: Coca-Cola Co. Meeting, March 1, 1971; 161678 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Boards: Coca-Cola Co. Meeting, May 4, 1971; 161679 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Boards: Coca-Cola Co. Meeting, August 2, 1971; 161680 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Boards: Coca-Cola Co. Meeting, November 15, 1971; 161681 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Boards: Coca-Cola Co. Meeting, March 6, 1972; 161682 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Boards: Coca-Cola Co. Meeting, May 2, 1972; 161683 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Boards: Coca-Cola Co. Meeting, August 7, 1972; 161684 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Boards: Coca-Cola Co. Meeting, November 20, 1972; 161685 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Boards: Coca-Cola Co. Meeting, March 5, 1973; 161686 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Boards: Coca-Cola Co. Meeting, May 8, 1973; 161687 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Boards: Coca-Cola Co. Meeting, August 6, 1973; 161688 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Boards: Coca-Cola Co. Meeting, November 19, 1973; 161689 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Boards: Coca-Cola Co. Meeting, March 4, 1974; 161694 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors, 1982; 161695 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Management Stewardship Report, 1984; 161696 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Management Stewardship Report, 1985; 161697 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Management Stewardship Report, 1986; 161698 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Management Stewardship Report, 1987; 161699 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Management Stewardship Report, 1988; 161700 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Management Stewardship Report, 1989; 161701 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Management Stewardship Report, 1990; 161702 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Management Stewardship Report, 1991; 161703 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Management Stewardship Report, 1992; 161704 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Management Stewardship Report, 1993; 161705 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Management Stewardship Report, 1994; 161706 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Management Stewardship Report, 1995; 161707 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Board of Directors Meeting: Management Stewardship Report, 1996; 161708 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Board of Directors: The real Coke, the real story, 1986; 161709 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Boards: Coca Cola Co., Miscellaneous, 161710 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Bottlers: Atlanta Coca-Cola, Co., 1974; 161711 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Bottlers: Los Angeles, 161712 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Bottlers: New York, 161713 (Box 3, Folder 20-21)
    - Bottlers: Thomas, Inc., 161714 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Budget, 1987; 161715 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Columbia Pictures Industries, Inc., 1982-83; 161716 (Box 3, Folder 24-27)
    - Committee on Directors, March-August 1981; 161718 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Committee on Directors, September-November 1981; 161717 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Committee on Directors, 1982; 161719 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Executive Committee, 1982; 161720 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Committees: Management, 1970-71; 161721 (Box 3, Folder 32-33)
    - Committees: Management, 1972; 161722 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Committees: Management, 161723 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Committees: Corporate Management, 161724 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Committees: Corporate Organization, 1969-72; 161725 (Box 4, Folder 4-5)
    - Committees: Corporate Organization, 1973-74; 161726 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Committees: Corporate Organization, 161727 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
    - Committees: Policy Review, 161728 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, November 10-30, 1967; 161729 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, November 30-December 29, 1967; 161730 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, January 1-31, 1968; 161731 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, February 1-20, 1968; 161732 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, February 21-28, 1968; 161733 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, March 1-29, 1968; 161734 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, April 1-30, 1968; 161735 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, May 1-31, 1968; 161736 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, June 4-29, 1968; 161737 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, July 1-29, 1968; 161738 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, August 1-30, 1968; 161739 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, September 3 - October 31, 1968; 161740 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, November 4-December 30, 1968; 161741 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, January 2-February 28, 1969; 161742 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, March 3-May 23, 1969; 161743 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, June-October 1969; 161744 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, November-December 1969; 161745 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, January-April 1970; 161746 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, May-August 1970; 161747 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, September-December 1970; 161748 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, January-May 1971; 161749 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: Chronological, June 1971; 161750 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence: Confidential, 1971; 161751 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence: Confidential, 1972; 161752 (Box 4, Folder 33-34)
    - Correspondence: Confidential, 1973; 161753 (Box 4, Folder 35-36)
    - Individual Correspondence: Confidential [Duncan] move from London to Atlanta, 1972; 161817 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Individual Correspondence: Austin, J. Paul, 1970-73; 161754 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Individual Correspondence: Daljit Singh/New Delhi, 1981-82; 161755 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Individual Correspondence: Roberto C. Goizueta, 1980-81; 161782 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Individual Correspondence: Roberto C. Goizueta, 1982; 161783 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Individual Correspondence: Roberto C. Goizueta, 1983; 161784 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Individual Correspondence: John Talley, 1967-69; 161785 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Individual Correspondence: John Talley, 1969-71; 161786 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Individual Correspondence: R.W. Woodruff, 1973-74; 161787 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1981-82; 161788 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1982; 161789 (Box 5, Folder 8-9)
    - Diversification: American Express, 161790 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Europe: Long-range planning, 161791 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Europe: Long-range planning, additional material, 161792 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - External relations: German advertisements, 1968; 161811 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Long-range planning presentation, August 28, 1970; 161793 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Long-range planning, 1972; 161794 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Management Charter, 1971; 161795 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Memoranda: Chief Executive Officer, [1972]; 161812 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Memoranda: Corporate Organization, 1971; 161813 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Memoranda: Corporate Structure, 1971; 161814 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Memoranda: Domestic Bottling Subsidiaries, 1972; 161815 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Memoranda: Duncan decline re-election as President, 1974; 161816 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Memoranda: Goizueta to Board of Directors, 1989, 1990, 1995, 1997; 161826 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Memoranda: Memos to the file, 1974; 161818 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Memoranda: Mini-Environmental Analysis, 1975; 161820 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Memoranda: Officer's Salaries, 161821 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Memoranda: Personal & Confidential, 1974; 161819 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Memoranda: Reorganization Discussions, 1974; 161823 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Memoranda: Special Task Force (RDH), [1972]; 161824 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Memoranda: [Regarding] Woodruff, 1974; 161825 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous, 1971; 161796 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - New Enterprises Division, 161797 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Organizational Charts, 1973; 161798 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Printed Materials: Business Week, August 24, 1963; 161834 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Printed Materials: Chronological history and products, 161906 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Printed Materials: My years with General Motors, by Alfred P. Sloan, Jr., 161835 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Printed Materials: What to expect in the next 10 years Research Institute of America, 1975; 161907 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Rankings, salaries, etc., 161799 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Remarks: Allen & Company Investor Conference, July 9, 1993; 161837 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Remarks: Area Manager's Conference, October 22, 1964; 161838 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Remarks: Area Manager's Meeting, October 1968; 161839 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Remarks: Bottler Management Conferences, October 1972; 161840 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Remarks: Bottler Management Conferences, 1972; 161841 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Remarks: Bottlers Association, September 14, 1972; 161842 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Remarks: Bottlers Association, January 29, 1974; 161843 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Remarks: Mexico Bottler's Meeting, January 14, 1972; 161844 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Remarks: [Bottlers Munster], 161845 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Remarks: Bottling Co. Tennessee, March 30, 1971; 161846 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Remarks: The Changing Role of Business, May 9, 1973; 161847 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Remarks: Coca-Cola Europe, August 31-September 3, 1971; 161848 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Remarks: Corporate Conference, May 15, 1964; 161849 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Remarks: Corporate Engineering Conference, April 20, 1971; 161850 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Remarks: Dallas Security Analysts, December 1963; 161851 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Remarks: Division Managers Meeting, February 2, 1994; 161852 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Remarks: Duncan Foods, Co., 161853 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Remarks: Foods Divisions Brokers, May 30, 1973; 161854 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Remarks: Foresees Club, December 21, 1964; 161855 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Remarks: Foresees Club-Atlanta, December 14, 1965; 161856 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Remarks: Foresees Club, December 14, 1970; 161857 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Remarks: Fountain Department Meetings, March 14 and 22, 1972; 161858 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Remarks: Globalization and the Zeitgeist, January 16, 1992; 161859 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Remarks: Houston/Sales Meeting, August 23, 1967; 161860 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Remarks: International Advertising Association, June 20, 1968; 161861 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Remarks: Introduction of Robert Goizueta, January 16, 1992; 161862 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Remarks: Los Angeles Sales Conference, November 24, 1964; 161863 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Remarks: Management Committee, June 8, 1971; 161864 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Remarks: Marketing Division Meeting, October 2, 1970; 161865 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Remarks: Marketing Meeting, October 2, 1970; 161866 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Remarks: Multinational Advertising at Home Everywhere, 161867 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Remarks: National Conference of the Coca-Cola Co. Foods Division, 1971; 161868 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Remarks: 100 years of Looking Ahead, May 7, 1986; 161869 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Remarks: Oversees Managers Meeting, October 6, 1971; 161870 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Remarks: A perspective on the world of Coca-Cola, October 20, 1972; 161871 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Remarks: The power of differentiation, 161872 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Remarks: Profile of the Coca-Cola Co. in 1990, November 6, 1985; 161873 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Remarks: Project Alert, 1971; 161874 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Remarks: A reaffirmation of Leadership, 161875 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Remarks, June 29, 1970; 161876 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Remarks, October 6, 1972; 161877 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Remarks: River Oaks Country Club, December 11, 1970; 161878 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Remarks: Trust Company Officers Group, November 29, 1972; 161879 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Remarks: University of Alabama, 1970; 161880 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Remarks: Woodruff's 50th Anniversary Dinner, April 28, 1973; 161881 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Remarks: Young President's Organization, October 20, 1970; 161882 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Remarks: Miscellaneous material, 1963, 1966; 161883 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Remarks: Miscellaneous material, 1965-1970; 161884 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Remarks: Miscellaneous material, 161885 (Box 6, Folder 39-43)
    - Remarks: Notes on Corporate seminar, November 2-5, 1970; 161886 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Remarks: Judge Thurman Arnold to dinner of Coca-Cola men, December 4, 1948; 161888 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Remarks: Four Red Herrings by Paul Foley, 1971; 161889 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Remarks: 1985 - It was a very good year by Roberto C. Goizueta, December 3, 1985; 161887 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Remarks: General Comments on pollution by Roberto C. Goizueta, 1970; 161890 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Remarks: Tribute dinner for Robert W. Woodruff by Roberto C. Goizueta, 1984; 161891 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Remarks: Roberto C. Goizueta, 1983; 161892 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Remarks: What makes a loser by Roberto C. Goizueta, May 16, 1984; 161893 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Remarks: What makes a loser - revisited by Roberto C. Goizueta, October 7, 1985; 161894 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Remarks: Closing remarks by A.W. Hughes, Jr., June 1, 1971; 161895 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Remarks: Presentation for 14th Japan/Texas Conference by Masaomi Iwamura, September 7, 1987; 161896 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Remarks: Donald R. Keough, 1965, 1972, 1974; 161897 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Remarks: Donald R. Keough to Rotary Club of Philadelphia, October 22, 1975; 161898 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Remarks: Response of H.B. Nicholson, December 4, 1973; 161899 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Remarks: International advertising for products of Coca-Cola, Co. by H.B. Nicholson, Jr., June 20, 1968; 161900 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Remarks: Coca-Cola Export Corporation V.P. remarks by Klaus Putter, 1970-71, 1973; 161901 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Remarks: C.A. Shillinglaw remarks, March 3, 1976; 161902 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Remarks: on Duncan's behalf, May 22, 1973; 161903 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Report: Financial, December 1971; 161800 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Report: Financial, December 1972; 161801 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Report: Financial, June 1973; 161802 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Report: Financial, August 1973; 161803 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Report: Financial, November 1973; 161804 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Report: Financial, December 1973; 161805 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Report: Financial, March 1974; 161806 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Report: Jacobson Study, 1973; 161910 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Report: Jacobson Study [portion for Duncan file], 1973; 161911 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Report: Net Profit summary, March 1973, June 1973; 161807 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Report: Project Alpha, February 1968; 161808 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Report: Project Alpha, March 5, 1968; 161809 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Report: Project Cap, November 1966; 161810 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Report: Stock reports, 1963-64; 161904 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Report: Strategy statement, September 6, 1973; 161908 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Report: Tone at the top, 1995; 161905 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Board appointments, 161935
    - Boston Consulting, Inc., 161948 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Cameron Iron Works, Inc. - Board of Directors, 1982-83; 161949 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Cameron Iron Works, Inc. - Compensation Committee, 1982-83; 161950 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Southern Railway, 1972; 161951 (Box 7, Folder 11-12)
    - Trust Company of Georgia, 1969-73; 161952 (Box 7, Folder 13-15)
- Series II. Rice University, 1972-1996, 160579
  Access restrictions
  The material in this series is restricted until 2040.
  - Board of Governors (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Board of Governors (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Board of Governors (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Rice Alumni Meeting, 1974-03-01 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Matching Gifts, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Fund Council (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Departmental Annual Reports A-G (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Series III. Deputy Secretary of Defense and Secretary of Energy appointments, 1977-1981, 160577
  - Sub-Series I. Bound Volumes, 1979-1981, n.d.; 143778
    - Charles William Duncan, Jr. Nomination Hearing, July 30, 1979; 143791 (Box 16)
    - Forward Schedule for the Secretary of Energy, Charles W. Duncan, Jr., August 24, 1979-January 19, 1981; 143782 (Box 16)
    - 1981 DOE Authorization Hearings, January 31, 1980; 143783 (Box 16)
    - Oil Import Fees: The Administration of the Program and its Impact Hearings, April 24; May 9, 14, 1980; 143784 (Box 16)
    - National Energy Security Corporation Hearings, September 21, 24, October 11, 18, 1979; 143785 (Box 16)
    - 1980 Economic Report of the President Hearings, January 30, February 1, 5, 6, and 7, 1980; 143786 (Box 16)
    - National Energy Security Corporation Hearings, September 21, 24, October 11, and 18, 1979; 143787 (Box 16)
    - Economic Issues for Fiscal Year 1981 Hearings, January 29, 30, 31; February 5, 6, 7, 19, 20, 21, 28; March 5, and 6, 1980; 143788 (Box 16)
    - Oversight of the Structure and Management of the Department of Energy Hearings, July 24, 31, and October 25, 1979; 143789 (Box 16)
    - Fiscal Year 1981 Authorization for the Department of Energy and the Federal Energy Regulatory Commission Hearings, February 8, 11, 12, 13, 20, and 29, 1980; 143790 (Box 16)
    - Filling the Strategic Petroleum Reserve: Oversight; and H.R. 7252: Use of the Naval Petroleum Reserves, April 25, May 21, and September 15, 1980; 143792 (Box 16)
    - Proposed Fiscal Year 1981 Budget Request Hearings, February 4 and 6, 1980; 143793 (Box 16)